はっ はっ はっ…
Sky High isn't doing so good lately.
スカイハイって
最近パッとしないよな？
His days are over.
あいつの時代は終わったっしょ
You're right. It's all about Tiger & Barnaby now!
やっぱ時代は
タイガーアンド
バーナビー！
Here he is!
でたあああ！
Sky High, the former King of Heroes, and current Wind Wizard!
キング オブ ヒーロー 改め
風の魔術師
スカイハイ！
If this keeps up,
このままでは３位に転落するのも
時間の問題だぞ
it'll only be a matter of time before you slip to third place.
I'm sorry.
すみません
あっ
yabureta PAGE wa ubawaretanda yo
That torn page was stolen,
破れたページは
奪われたんだよ
dokoka de otoshita oboe wa nai kara
since I don't remember ever dropping it anywhere.
何処かで落とした
覚えはないから
iwakan mo nai hodo kirei ni nai soko ni wa
In the place where the page used to be,
違和感もないほど
綺麗にないそこには
yume to iu nano shou ga tashikani atta
there was a chapter entitled "Dreams."
夢という名の章が確かにあった
nani wo nikumeba ii? kako ka jibun jishin ka
But who should I blame? The past? Myself?
何を憎めばいい？
過去か自分自身か
dekireba hoka no dareka de are
If possible, I hope it's someone else.
出来れば他の誰かであれ
monogatari no bokura ga sono mirai wo omou no wa
We, the characters in the story, think of the future.
物語の僕らが
その未来想うのは
nakushita ato demo shuyaku wa kawarenai kara
Because even after we're gone, the main character can't change.
失くした後でも
主役は変われないから
shousan nante sarenakutatte tashikana kyou ga aru nara
Even if I'm not praised, as long as today is here,
賞賛なんてされなくたって
確かな今日があるなら
yume nante namae no shou wa ikura demo tsukurerunda
I can make as many chapters as I want entitled "Dreams."
夢なんて名前の章は
いくらでも創れるんだ
ふんっ ふっ
He sure is energetic today.
随分熱心ね
What's got into him?
どうしちゃったんだろ
ふんっ
うへへ
それに比べて
On the other hand...
That one is quiet today.
こっちは随分大人しいわね
早く行きますよ　虎徹さん
Let's get going, Kotetsu.
Hey, Bunny.
よう バニー
Again with the excessive workout?
また無茶なトレーニングして
それじゃ夜までもちませんよ？
At this rate, you won't last through the day.
大丈夫だって
Don't worry! I've been feeling great lately.
最近なんか調子いいし
Stop joking around and get ready.
ふざけないで支度してください
取材に遅刻します
We're going to be late for our interview.
よっしゃ 行くか！
All right! Let's go!
はあ 相変わらずお忙しいこと
They're busy as always.
Don't you agree, Sky High?
ね？　スカイハイ？
はあ…
I've never seen him sigh like that.
あんな深いため息初めて見た
そりゃそうだ
Who can blame him?
ん？
He probably has mixed feelings
やつからしたら複雑だろ
about seeing those two take the spotlight.
あいつらの活躍は
No enemies can beat them!
向かうところ敵なし　最強無敵の
They're the invincible Tiger & Barnaby!
タイガーアンドバーナビー
But against tough stains, they'll use this to...
そんな二人でも倒せない
手強い汚れを
Knock-knock-knock out!
ノック ノック ノックアウト！
洗剤界のニューヒーロー
The new Hero of cleanliness, Super Dish!
スーパー ディッシュ！
Now on sale!
新発売
はあ…
あ ジョン　待ちなさい
Oh! John! Come back here!
くっ
あっ
ジョン　やめなさい
Stop that, John!
お怪我はありませんか？
Are you okay?
I am fine.
大丈夫
Thank goodness.
良かった
ああ 隣に座っても？
Oh, mind if I sit next to you?
ええ
No.
お騒がせして すみませんでした
I'm sorry for all the commotion.
Not at all.
いいえ
あ…
What a nice place.
いい場所ですね
あっ そうだ
Oh, yeah.
Please.
良かったら
これ
Have one.
あっ
ごめんなさい
I'm sorry.
君もＮＥＸＴなのかい？
Are you a NEXT too?
I don't know.
分からない
I see. Your powers just awakened.
そうか
まだ能力が目覚めたばかりなんだね
大丈夫
It's all right.
最初はコントロールが
難しいかもしれないが
Controlling them will be difficult at first,
but you'll quickly get used to it.
すぐに慣れる
ちなみに 私が能力に目覚めたのは
By the way, my powers awakened
when I was eighteen years old, during summer.
18歳の夏だった
え〜　バーナビーさんが
ＮＥＸＴの能力に目覚めたのは
Mr. Barnaby, when did your NEXT powers awaken?
いつごろなんですか？
It seems I already had them when I was two.
２歳のときには すでにあったようです
抱くのをやめると
I'm told my mother would often say
泣いて能力を発動させるから困ったと
she had trouble with me, because I would start crying
and activate my powers whenever she'd put me down.
母はよくもらしていたみたいです
Sounds like a pretty cute story.
なんだか
ほっこりさせられるエピソード
Don't you think so, Mr. Wild Tiger?
ですね？　ワイルドタイガーさん？
ですね〜
Oh, yeah!
Did we have to do that in swimsuits?!
って
水着でやる必要あったのかよ？
ごめんね〜
So sorry.
グラビア撮影と取材の時間が
I couldn't schedule the swimsuit photo shoot
別々に取れなかったんだよ〜
and the interview at different times.
いや 俺らアイドルじゃないんですよ？
We're not super stars.
Don't you hate doing all this?
こんなんばっか 嫌だよな〜？
いや それが全然
Actually, I don't mind at all.
What?!
え？
In fact, I'm enjoying each and every day.
むしろ毎日楽しいんです
はあ？
You are?
今までと
景色が違って見えるっていうか
Everything I see and do feels so different now,
復讐のために生きてたときとは
別ものみたいなんです
compared to when I was living for revenge.
悪いけど 急いでもらっていいかな？
Mind if I ask you two to hurry up?
You can take your break in the car.
休憩は車の中で頼むよ
There's still more?
まだ何かあんのか
スケジュール　見てないんですか？
Didn't you look at the schedule?
次はバラエティ番組の収録
Next, you two are appearing on a variety show,
そのあとは
お正月アニメのゲスト声優
then you're doing a guest voice role
for a New Year's Anime special.
ちょと待ってください！
Now hold on a second! What are we trying to become here?!
俺たちどこ向かってんですか？
ヒーローですけど？
We're supposed to be Heroes!
まあ いいじゃないの
Oh, don't get so upset.
It's not like you're getting called into action.
出動要請もないんだしさ
That's true, but...
そうですけど…
ねえ あれって
Hey, isn't that...
ん？
Sky High?
スカイハイ？
What is he doing?
何やってんだろ？
あらやだ　あんたたち知らないの？
Oh gosh, you didn't know?
Huh?
は？
That's Sky High's night job.
スカイハイの夜のお仕事
Ever since he became a Hero,
彼ヒーローになってから
毎晩ああやってパトロールしてるのよ
he's been patrolling the city every night.
Wow, he's such a boy scout.
うわあ 真面目
Thank you very much!
ありがとうございました
It's true! I've been feeling great lately!
いや ほんっと最近調子 いいんスよ
んん？
この前も能力発動したら こう
Even the other day, I activated my powers and I went flying,
バーっと飛び上がって
ビューっとなって
like "whoosh," then "boom," and "bang!"
バーっとなって
それじゃまったく伝わりませんよ
You're not making sense.
ラジオなんですから
Remember, we're on radio.
いや とにかく いつも以上に
すんごいパワーが出ちゃったんですよ
Anyway, I had a lot more power than usual!
You could say that Wild Tiger is still evolving!
まっ ワイルドタイガーは
進化し続けるってことですかね？
How wonderful. How thrilling.
素敵　ゾクゾクしちゃう
いやあ あなたも素敵
もうゾクゾクしちゃう
I'm thrilled at how wonderful you are too.
あははは
あは あははは
ぐっ！
What an idiot!
ばっかみたい！
朝から仕事なんて大変だね
It must be rough working so early in the morning.
はあ…
まあまあ 落ち込みなさんな
Now, now, don't get depressed.
You can still make a comeback as number one.
また一位に返り咲けばいいじゃない
いや 私が悩んでるのは
Comeback? I was actually thinking about love issues.
恋の悩みだが
えええー！
What?!
スカイハイが恋？
Sky High is in love?!
あ〜ら 恋のシーズンね
Oh dear. Everyone's falling in love these days.
最近元気なかったのはそのせい？
Is that why you've been depressed lately?
ちょっと 水臭いじゃない
How could you not tell us? Who is she?!
どこの誰なのよ？
いや その…
Well, umm...
When did you meet her?
いつ出会ったの？
３日ほど前に
About three days ago.
もう好きって言った？
Did you already say you like her?
Of course not!
そんなまさか
もう 奥手なんだから
Jeez, you're so shy!
仕方ない　私たちが
恋のアドバイスしてあげる
All right, then! We'll give you some advice on love!
うん
Yeah!
Please go easy on me.
あはは…　お手柔らかに
All right!
よし
まずは笑顔
First off, smile!
No woman could resist a smile from a hot guy!
イケメンに微笑まれて
嬉しくない女子はいない！
やあ こんばんわ
Hey, good evening.
Hi.
はい
僕だったら
褒めてもらえると嬉しいかな
If I was her, I would like it if a boy said something nice about me.
That hair band... It has a very nice color of red.
そのカチューシャ
赤くてとても素敵だ
似合ってるよ
It looks good on you.
赤が好きなのかい？
Do you like red?
No.
いいえ
I see.
そう…
Girls have a weakness for physical contact!
女子はスキンシップに弱いの
自然な振る舞いで ボディタッチよ！
Touch her in a casual way!
くっ…
くっ
ぐっ
いっ んっ
Well, see you around.
じゃあ また…
Can you look towards the camera, please?
すみませ〜ん　目線お願いしま〜す
こっちも〜
Mine too!
We have a question for you two.
では おふた方に質問です
一番尊敬している人は誰ですか？
Who is the person you admire most?
俺は当然 レジェンドさんだ
I'd have to say Mr. Legend!
はあ…
Oh...
Because he's cool!
理由は かっこいいからだ
Uh-huh...
ふ〜ん
続いてバーナビーさん　お願いします
And you, Mr. Barnaby?
I suppose that would be my parents.
僕は両親ですかね
I see.
なるほど
僕の両親は
ロボットの研究をしていました
My parents were doing research on robots.
Their dream was to create a robot that could save people
人を助けるロボットを作り
世の中を平和にしたい
それが二人の夢でした
and make the world peaceful.
They were great partners at work and at home.
二人は仕事でも家庭でも
良きパートナーだったんです
そんな両親を今でも尊敬しています
I look up to my parents even now.
That's a great answer.
良いコメントだな
うん
Yeah.
そうだな
I'm really surprised.
いや〜　それにしても驚いたよ
ご両親がロボットの研究していたなんて
Your parents worked in robotics?
ええ
Yes.
研究所に何度も連れて行って
もらったのを 覚えています
I remember them taking me to their lab many times.
They looked so cool when they were working.
二人の働く姿が 凄くかっこよくて
本当に 両親が大好きでした
I really loved my parents.
俺も楓にそんな風に言われてえな
Wish Kaede would say something like that about me.
I'm sure she does.
きっと娘さんだって
いやいや
No way. Whenever I call her, all she does is complain.
電話しても文句ばっかりだぜ？
Like how my stories are outdated.
話題が古い〜とか
Or that my jokes are dumb.
つまんない冗談言うな〜とか
Or that my beard is lame.
ひげがだっせえとか
That's for sure.
確かに
お前なあ
Come on...
ん？
おい あれ
Hey, look up there.
ヒーローＴＶ
HERO TV?
The suspect is on the run with hostages.
犯人は人質を連れたまま 未だ逃走中
And Sky High... is in pursuit!
それを追うのは
スカイハイ！
Can he make a successful arrest today?
今日こそ 活躍することができるのか？
Why weren't we informed?
何で俺たちに連絡ないんだよ？
故障ですかね？
Is it malfunctioning?
No, I had you two excused.
いや 辞退しておいたから
え？
What?!
You two have been quite busy with interviews lately, right?
ここんところ取材で忙しかったでしょ？
With the Second League Heroes around,
２部の連中もいるんだし
君たちが出動するほどの事件じゃ…
I decided it wasn't worth taking your time to...
Are you being serious?
それホンキで言ってるんスか？
ん？
Our job as Heroes is to save the people!
市民を助けてこそのヒーローでしょ！
ＴＶの前でニコニコするのは
俺たちの仕事じゃないですよ！
Not to smile in front of the cameras!
虎徹さん　落ち着いて
Calm down, Kotetsu!
決まった〜！
She did it!
Dragon Kid has captured the suspect!
ドラゴンキッドが犯人を確保！
さあ！
And Origami Cyclone manages to get some points
人質を救出して
ちゃっかりポイントゲットの
折紙サイクロン
for saving the hostages.
The younger Heroes are taking the spotlight this season.
今期は 若いヒーローの
活躍が目立っています
一方 終盤 突如の失速
Meanwhile, Sky High had a sudden crash at the end.
He wasn't able to do anything again.
今日も活躍することができませんでした
What has happened to Sky High?!
一体どうしたんでしょうか？
スカイハイ
あっ
まさか こんな時間に
君に会えるとは思わなかったよ
I didn't expect to find you at such a late hour.
ええ
Yes.
ちょっと私の話をしてもいいかな？
Mind if I talk a little about myself?
ええ
No.
私はね　最近まで仕事で
ずっとトップだったんだ
You see, until recently I was the best at my job.
But not anymore.
しかし今は違う
Dropping in rank doesn't really bother me.
別に順位が下がったことは
どうでもいいんだ
ただ もう一度皆の期待に添えるのか
But I'm just not sure if I can live up to...
everyone's expectations anymore.
それが不安なんだよ
I failed once and learned how powerless I am the hard way.
一度失敗して
自分の無力さを痛感してしまって
When I think that I may not be able to do anything,
また自分は何もできないんじゃないか
そう思うと 怖くて
I become afraid and unable to move.
身体が動かなくなって
I feel pathetic.
自分が情けないよ
The way I'm performing now...
こんな私なんて
It's the same as if I weren't around.
いなくても同じだ
なぜ？
Why?
Even if I'm around, I'll end up disappointing everyone.
私がいても 皆を失望させるだけだ
Why?
なぜ？
Why? Because...
なぜって それは…
Why?
なぜ？
あっ
あ…
You're trying to force me to confront the truth, aren't you?
私に
気づかせてくれようとしてるんだね？
It's true.
確かにそうだ
I just made up excuses and didn't do anything about it.
自分に言い訳ばかりして
私は何も行動していなかった
ありがとう　そし…
Thank you. And...
It's late. I'll walk you home.
もう遅い　家まで送ろう
大丈夫
I am fine.
あ… へ 変なこと言ってすまない
Sorry for saying such strange things.
それじゃ また明日
See you tomorrow.
Until tomorrow.
明日また
There you are, Cis.
探したぞ　シス
心配したんだぞ？
You had me worried.
ごめんなさい
I'm sorry.
Okay!
よし
あ〜あ　今日も取材で終わったか
Another day wasted with just interviews.
Doing interviews is also an important part of our job.
取材だって大切な仕事ですよ？
でもこれじゃ身体がなまっちまうだろ？
But if we keep this up, we'll get out of shape.
まったく…
You know... You could use a lesson from Mr. Sky High.
スカイハイさんの爪の垢でも
煎じて飲んだらどうです？
ええ？
Huh?
Even when he was so busy like this, he never once complained.
こんな生活を続けていても
彼はグチなんて一度も
もらしませんでしたよ？
そうだけどよ〜
I know that, but...
What the heck?!
おあっ　なんだ？
くっ　シス！　やめろ！
Cis, stop!
う…
ひいっ
Are you all right?
だいじょぶですか？
You're!
君は？
She seems to be a power-type NEXT.
パワー系ＮＥＸＴのようですね
Are you serious?
まじかよ
Heroes...
ヒーロー…
えっ
Heroes...
ヒーロー…
くあっ　ぐっ
そう　こういうのが
ヒーローの仕事だよ
Finally! I get to do some real Hero work.
おい　少しは落ち…
Hey, try to calm down a little!
おわたっ おわ！
だっ
ヒーロー…
Heroes...
Looks like reasoning is not an option.
説得は無理そうですね
Guess not!
だな
What?!
何？
うわっ　うおおおお
ぐあっ
くっ
凄いパワーだ
What incredible power.
くっ　何なんだ　こいつは？
What the hell is wrong with her?!
おわあっ
Amazing...
凄い
She's amazing!
凄いぞ！
ぐあっ
くっ
ああ！
Yes.
ええ　いいえ
No.
I'm sorry.
ごめんなさい
I don't know.
分からない
I am fine.
大丈夫
Yes.
はい
She's not human!
こいつ 人間じゃない！
I didn't know such an advanced android existed.
こんな高性能のアンドロイドが
存在していたなんて
She didn't just happen to exist.
していたわけではありません
I brought her into existence.
私が存在させたのです
えっ
You created her?
あなたがこれを？
I realized the limitless possibilities of androids.
私はアンドロイドに無限の可能性を
感じていましてね
Androids will surpass humans... No, they will even surpass NEXT.
アンドロイドは人間を超える
いや ＮＥＸＴをも超える
存在になりうる
そこで すべてのものの頂点に立つ
I've been conducting research to create the most powerful being
最強の存在を造ろうと
研究を続けてきました
that will stand above us all.
その成果をすべてつぎ込んだのが
I poured all of my results into Cis.
シスなのです
She is my masterpiece.
彼女こそ私の最高傑作
ヒーロー
Heroes!
くっ やめろ！
Stop!
くっ ヒーローがなんだってんだよ！
What about Heroes?!
What do you want?
目的はなんだ？
Why is she going after us Heroes?
なぜしつようにヒーローを狙う？
She's not really going after you.
別に狙っているわけではありません
ちょっとした誤作動が
起こっていましてね
She's just sort of malfunctioning.
な…
彼女にはヒーローのデータを
比較対象として入れてあるのです
She has data on Heroes to draw from.
地球上で最強になるには
In order to become the most powerful in the world,
ヒーローを超える
存在にならくてはいけませんからね
she needed to be able to surpass the Heroes.
But then a few days ago...
それが先日
While I was transporting her,
輸送中に落雷事故にあいまして
there was an accident involving lightning.
その隙をついて
シスは車から飛び出してしまった
Cis took that opportunity to jump out of the car.
When I finally found and retrieved her...
彼女を探し出し 回収してみると
感電事故により
Her system appeared to have been damaged
一時的に
システムが故障したのでしょう
by the electrical shock.
ヒーローに関わるものを認識すると
Whenever she recognizes something Hero-related,
戦闘モードに切り替わってしまう
she goes into battle mode.
Well, that about sums it up.
まっ それだけのことです
But this is better than I had imagined!
しかし想像以上ですよ
ヒーローとここまで互角に戦えるとは
I never expected her to be able to fight this well against Heroes.
I must thank your parents for this.
あなたのご両親に
感謝しなくてはなりませんね
You still don't recognize me?
まだ私を思い出しませんか？
あ あなたは…
You're!
I am Rotwang. I worked for your parents.
ご両親の部下だったロトワングですよ
Cis is based on their research.
シスのベースはおふた方の
研究が元になっているのです
研究は私に受け継がれ
進化を遂げました
Their research was passed on to me,
and I took it to the next level.
Your parents would have been pleased.
あなたのご両親もお喜びに…
そんなはずはない！
No, they wouldn't!
My parents...
父と母は
wanted to make an android that could save people!
人間を助けるアンドロイドを
造りたいと言っていた
They didn't want to make a weapon of destruction like this!
二人が造りたかったのは
こんな戦闘兵器じゃない！
私は彼らの研究を進化させたのですよ？
I made advances on their work.
研究者として望んでいるはずだ！
As researchers, that is what they would have wanted!
うう…
どあああ！
あっ
ごめんなさい
I'm sorry.
I don't know.
分からない
I am fine.
大丈夫
Unless you smash her to bits,
木っ端微塵にでもしない限り
シスは街中を破壊し続けるでしょう
Cis will continue to destroy the city.
The city is plastered with the faces of Heroes.
街にはヒーローの顔が
あふれていますからね
そんな！
No!
You... damn... bastard!
こ…
ん…
にゃ…
ろおおおお！
くっ
Stay put!
大人しくしろ！
な？
What?!
どわ！
どわっ くっ
どは！
Come back!
待て！
あ痛てて…
Oww...
I thought I activated my power at the same time as Bunny.
バニーと一緒に発動させたはずだよな？
What's going on?
どうなってんだ？
Damn it!
くそっ
She can even fly?
飛行能力まであるのか
Stop right there!
そこまでだ！
あっ
あれ ス…
Sky High!
スカイハイ！
Let me handle this one!
ここは私に任せろ！
What kind of an android is this?!
なんだ？　このアンドロイドは？
ぐっ
くうっ
ぐう！
くっ
ふおおおおおお！
でやああ！
I will not allow you to wreak further havoc!
これ以上 暴れさせはしないぞ！
The only way to stop her now is to destroy her!
止めるには
もう破壊するしかありません
It's over!
とどめだ！
Sky...
スカーイ
ハーイ！
High!
う あ…　ああ…
I did it.
やった
I did it!
やったぞ！
ふんっ ふんっ
He sure looks energetic today.
今日は随分熱心ね
Well, I'm glad he's feeling better.
まあ 元気になって
良かった良かった
それに比べてこっちは…
Wish I could say the same for him.
I wonder if something happened.
何かあったのかしら？
Do you think it'll happen again?
また起こると思いますか？
ん？
Huh?
Something like last night's incident with the android.
昨夜のような アンドロイドの事件が…
だいじょぶか？　バニー？
Are you all right, Bunny?
両親の研究が あんな形で
続いていたのはショックです
I'm shocked that my parents' research
was being continued in that way.
でも 父と母が
本当に何を望んでいるのか
But I could never know what my parents really wanted.
僕には分からない
I feel disappointed that I don't know what they wanted.
二人の思いを理解できないのが
やるせなくて…
What's wrong, you two?
どうした 二人とも？
What good will it do if we Heroes are depressed?
私たちヒーローが
元気でなくてどうする？
That would be setting a bad example for the people!
市民に示しがつかないぞ と
あ…　そうですね
You're right.
Let's continue to work hard for the people of the city!
これからも市民のために
頑張っていこうではないか！
だな
Yeah.
Now then...
さてと
Oh, where are you going?
あら？　どこへ行くの？
I'm going to go thank her.
彼女にお礼を言いにね
Huh?
え？
You mean to the woman you were talking about?!
もしかして例の彼女と？
やはあああ　うまくいってんの？
Oh, my! Then it worked out?! Go get'em! Fire!
ヒュー ヒュー
ファイヤーヒュー
灰色に染まる街の片隅で
hai iro ni somaru machi no katasumi de souzou dake no yume wo miteita
In an obscure corner of the ashen city, I was having a surreal dream.
想像だけの夢をみていた
存在する事の意味を
sonzai suru koto no imi wo nantonaku kangaehajimeta
I started to think about the meaning of existence.
なんとなく考え始めた
But I never know
BUT, I NEVER KNOW.
But, I never know.
myself＆夢＆
MYSELF AND yume AND TRUE AND ANYMORE
Myself & dreams & truth & anymore.
true＆Anymore
もう… もっと…
mou... motto...
At all...
こんな世界で私に聞いたの
konna sekai de watashi ni kita no ittai nani ga dekiru no ka wo
I asked myself what one can do in a world like this.
一体何が出来るのかを
あなたの笑顔が教えてくれたような
anata no egao ga oshiete kureta youna sonna kigashita kara
And I felt that your smiling face could teach me the answer.
そんな気がしたから
光を見つけたような
hikari wo mitsuketa youna itami ni furerareru
And enabled me to be touched by the pain of finding light.
痛みに触れられる
そう そんな気がした
sou, sonna kigashita
Yes, that was the feeling.
人は皆儚い夢を
hito wa mina hakanai yume wo kono te ni ireru tame ni
In pursuing their fleeting dreams,
この手に入れる為に
永遠の真実さえ
eien no shinjitsu sae miushinau
people lose sight of the eternal truth.
見失う
消えない悲しい明日に
kienai kanashii asu ni hikari wo kureta no wa daredemo naku tatta hitori
No one made me realize that there is a light that never dims but you,
光をくれたのは
誰でもなく たった一人
過去も未来も
shinjitai
I want to believe.
kako mo mirai mo wakachiaeru zutto
always sharing the past and the future.
分かち合えるずっと
よう
いや〜 久しぶりですね
Hey...
Wow, long time no see!
急に連絡きたんで 驚きましたよ
I was surprised to suddenly hear from you!
ちょっと聞きたいことがあってな
There was something I wanted to ask you.
Can I have what he's having?
は？
Huh?
お前 最近変わったことはないか？
Have you felt any different lately?
え？
いや 特には…
Huh?
Not really.
ああ！　強いて言えば
Well, the other day my power did get a sudden boost.
この前急に能力が
パワーアップしたくらいですかね
But that's about it.
そのとき ５分経たずに
Did your Hundred Power end before your five minutes were up?
ハンドレッドパワーが
切れたりしなかったか？
え？
Huh?
落ち着いてよく聞けよ
Stay calm and listen to me.
もしかしたら お前の能力は
減退し始めているかもしれん
Your powers might be declining.
減退？
Declining?
極めて稀なケースだが
It's very rare, but some NEXT gradually lose their powers.
段々と能力を失っていく
ＮＥＸＴがいるんだ
その前兆として
一度パワーが増幅する
Before their powers go, they become more powerful.
消える前の
Just like a candle before it goes out.
ろうそくのようにな…
あ…
お待たせいたしました
Here you go, sir!
ども！
TIGER ＆ BUNNYの
靴下は左から履く方
Hi! I'm Kotetsu, the member of Tiger & Bunny
虎徹です
また出やがったな ルナティック！
who puts on his left sock before the right one!
一体何者なんだ お前！
So you've shown up again, Lunatic!
あれ？　俺やられてない？
Who the hell are you?!
次回　TIGER ＆ BUNNY
Wait, am I losing here?
トゥ…　Truth lies at the…
Next time on Tiger & Bunny:
も もう１回やっていい？
Could I try that again?